questions_data = [
    {
        "question": "Convert the decimal number 8,391 to binary",
        "correct_answer": "10000011000111",
        "answer_choices": [
            "1010110111",
            "100000101011111",
            "110101000111",
            "10000011000111"
        ]
    },
{
    "question": "Convert 0x7B from hexadecimal to binary",
    "correct_answer": "0111 1011",
    "answer_choices": [
            "0111 0111",
            "1111 0111",
            "1111 1110",
            "0111 1011"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is 0xE in binary?",
    "correct_answer": "1110",
    "answer_choices": [
            "1100",
            "1011",
            "1111",
            "1110"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Convert the following decimal number, 4321, to binary.",
    "correct_answer": "1000011100001",
    "answer_choices": [
        "1000011100001",
        "101010101010",
        "101001000001",
        "110011001100"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Is 1011 1011 odd or even?",
    "correct_answer": "odd",
    "answer_choices": [
            "odd",
            "neutral",
            "even",
            "neither"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "For the following binary number, 0b1100111000, convert to hexadecimal.",
    "correct_answer": "0x338",
    "answer_choices": [
        "0x8E8",
        "0xC2C",
        "0x338",
        "0x4D4"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What are the next two numbers after 11 in base 12?",
    "correct_answer": "13,14",
    "answer_choices": [
            "12,13",
            "A,B",
            "10,11",
            "13,14",
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is 0x10 in base 10?",
    "correct_answer": "16",
    "answer_choices": [
            "20",
            "15",
            "10",
            "16"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is 0xFF in binary?",
    "correct_answer": "1111 1111",
    "answer_choices": [
            "1110 1111",
            "1111 0111",
            "1100 1100",
            "1111 1111"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is 0101 0101 in decimal?",
    "correct_answer": "85",
    "answer_choices": [
            "86",
            "101",
            "77",
            "85"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Convert 1010 1100 to decimal",
    "correct_answer": "172",
    "answer_choices": [
            "184",
            "162",
            "200",
            "172"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "For the following binary number, 0b1100111000, convert it to octal.",
    "correct_answer": "0o634",
    "answer_choices": [
        "0o147",
        "0o754",
        "0o634",
        "0o432"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Convert 1101 1100 to hexadecimal",
    "correct_answer": "0xDC",
    "answer_choices": [
            "0xDE",
            "0xBD",
            "0xCB",
            "0xDC"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Convert the following hexadecimal number, 0xB0B, to octal.",
    "correct_answer": "0o5613",
    "answer_choices": [
        "0o1234",
        "0o5613",
        "0o2467",
        "0o7105"
    ]
},
    {
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {s ∈ ℤ | s >= 1; s <= 10; s mod 3 = 0}",
    "correct_answer": "{3,6,9}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{1,4,7,10}",
            "{2,5,8}",
            "{3,6,9,12}",
            "{3,6,9}"
        ]
    },
{
    "question": "What is the result of 01101101 ⊕ 10001100?",
    "correct_answer": "11100001",
    "answer_choices": [
            "11001101",
            "10100111",
            "00011010",
            "11100001"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {s ∈ ℤ | s < 0; s mod 3 = 2}",
    "correct_answer": "{-4,-1}",
    "answer_choices": [
        "{-5,-2}",
        "{-4,-1}",
        "{-3,0}",
        "{-6,-3}"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 0x9F & 0x56?",
    "correct_answer": "0x16",
    "answer_choices": [
            "26",
            "0001 0110",
            "16",
            "0x16"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {s ∈ ℕ | s^2 <= 30}",
    "correct_answer": "{1,2,3,4,5}",
    "answer_choices": [
        "{1,2,3,4,5,6}",
        "{1,2,3,4,5}",
        "{1,2,3}",
        "{1,2,3,4}"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 1 ∧ 0?",
    "correct_answer": "0",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "1",
            "0"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {s ∈ ℤ | -10 <= s <= 10; s mod 7 = 0}",
    "correct_answer": "{-7,0,7}",
    "answer_choices": [
        "{-7,0,7}",
        "{-10,-3,4,11}",
        "{-6,-5,-4,-3,-2,-1,0,1,2,3,4,5,6}",
        "{-6,1,8}"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "¬q ∧ s ⇒ r is false when...",
    "correct_answer": "q=0, s=1, r=0",
    "answer_choices": [
            "q=1, s=0, r=1",
            "q=0, s=1, r=1",
            "q=1, s=1, r=0",
            "q=0, s=1, r=0"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {s ∈ W | 3 < s < 8; s mod 2 = 1}",
    "correct_answer": "{5,7}",
    "answer_choices": [
        "{5,7}",
        "{4,6}",
        "{5,6,7}",
        "{3,5}"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Which logic operator does the symbol, ∧ ,denote?",
    "correct_answer": "AND",
    "answer_choices": [
            "OR",
            "NOT",
            "XOR",
            "AND"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {s ∈ ℝ | 0 < s < 3; floor(s) mod 2 = 0}",
    "correct_answer": "{x ∈ ℝ | 0 < x < 1}",
    "answer_choices": [
        "{x ∈ ℝ | 0 < x < 1}",
        "{x ∈ ℝ | 1 < x < 2}",
        "{x ∈ ℝ | 0 < x < 2}",
        "{x ∈ ℝ | 0 < x < 3}"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 0xE4 XOR 0xB1?",
    "correct_answer": "0x55",
    "answer_choices": [
            "55",
            "0xD1",
            "0101 0101",
            "0x55"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Convert 15 into base 18, then list the next 5 numbers which follow",
    "correct_answer": "G,H,10,11,12",
    "answer_choices": [
            "16,17,18,1B,1C",
            "16,17,1B,1C,1D",
            "G,H,I,13,14",
            "G,H,10,11,12"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is 0xD4 in binary?",
    "correct_answer": "1101 0100",
    "answer_choices": [
            "1010 1110",
            "1101 0110",
            "1001 0010",
            "1101 0100"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Which set does the symbol, ℤ, denote?",
    "correct_answer": "Set of integers",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Set of real numbers",
        "Set of natural numbers",
        "Set of whole numbers",
        "Set of integers"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of ¬1001?",
    "correct_answer": "0110",
    "answer_choices": [
            "0101",
            "1100",
            "1001",
            "0110"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Which logic operator does the symbol, ⇔, denote?",
    "correct_answer": "Equivalence",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Implication",
        "AND",
        "OR",
        "Equivalence"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 1110 ∨ 0111?",
    "correct_answer": "1111",
    "answer_choices": [
            "1110",
            "1001",
            "1011",
            "1111"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, ∪ , denote in set theory?",
    "correct_answer": "Union",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Intersection",
        "Difference",
        "Complement",
        "Union"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What numbers are in {y|y < 7; y > 1; y/3 is an integer}?",
    "correct_answer": "{3, 6}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{2,5}",
            "{1,4,6}",
            "{2,3,4,6}",
            "{3, 6}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, ∈ , denote?",
    "correct_answer": "Is an element of",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Is not an element of",
        "Is a subset of",
        "Is an element of",
        "Is a superset of"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, ∩ , denote in set theory?",
    "correct_answer": "Intersection",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Union",
        "Difference",
        "Intersection",
        "Complement"
    ]
},
{
    "question": 'What is B - A?\nLet A = set of characters from "algorithm"\nLet B = set of characters from "rhythm"',
    "correct_answer": '{"y"}',
    "answer_choices": [
        '{"r","y"}',
        '{"h","m","t"}',
        '{"t","o","m"}',
        '{"y"}'
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, Φ , denote in set theory?",
    "correct_answer": "Empty set",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Universal set",
        "Subset",
        "Superset",
        "Empty set"
    ]
},
{
    "question": 'What is {7,2,5,9,1} ∩ {2,7,0,5}?',
    "correct_answer": '{2,5,7}',
    "answer_choices": [
            '{2,5,7,9,1,0}',
            '{9,1,0}',
            '{2,5,5,7}',
            '{2,5,7}'
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, | , denote in set theory?",
    "correct_answer": "Such that",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Intersection",
        "Union",
        "Complement",
        "Such that"
    ]
},
{
    "question": 'What is C - D?\nLet D = set of characters from "data"\nLet C = set of characters from "compute"',
    "correct_answer": '{"m","p","u","e"}',
    "answer_choices": [
        '{"m","p","u","e"}',
        '{"a","t"}',
        '{"d","a","t"}',
        '{"c","o","m","p","u","e"}'
    ]
},
{
    "question": 'What is the result of (0 ∧ 1) ⊕ (1 ∨ 1)?',
    "correct_answer": '1',
    "answer_choices": [
            '0',
            'True',
            'False',
            '1'
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, ' , denote in set theory?",
    "correct_answer": "Complement",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Intersection",
        "Union",
        "Complement",
        "Difference"
    ]
},
{
    "question": 'What is the result of 0x0F XOR 0xE5?',
    "correct_answer": '0xEA',
    "answer_choices": [
            '0xC0',
            '0xF0',
            '0x0A',
            '0xEA'
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, - , denote in set theory?",
    "correct_answer": "Difference",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Intersection",
        "Union",
        "Complement",
        "Difference"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "¬c ∧ d ⇒ e is false when...",
    "correct_answer": "c=0, d=1, e=0",
    "answer_choices": [
            "c=1, d=0, e=1",
            "c=0, d=1, e=1",
            "c=1, d=1, e=0",
            "c=0, d=1, e=0"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is a shorter way of writing B∪C - B∩C",
    "correct_answer": "B ⊕ C",
    "answer_choices": [
            "B ⇔ C",
            "B ∧ C",
            "B ∨ C",
            "B ⊕ C"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does the symbol, ¬ , denote in logic?",
    "correct_answer": "NOT",
    "answer_choices": [
        "AND",
        "OR",
        "XOR",
        "NOT"
    ]
},
{
    "question": 'What is the set of characters from "juxtaposition"',
    "correct_answer": '{"j","u","x","a","p","o","s","i","t","n"}',
    "answer_choices": [
            '{"j","u","x","a","p","o","s","i","t"}',
            '{"j","u","x","a","p","o","s","i","n"}',
            '{"j","u","x","a","p","o","s","t","n"}',
            '{"j","u","x","a","p","o","s","i","t","n"}'
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 0110 1001 + 0001 0111",
    "correct_answer": "1000 0000",
    "answer_choices": [
            "1010 1111",
            "124",
            "0111 1110",
            "1000 0000"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of x + y, where:\nx = [4 5 6]\ny = [1 2 3]",
    "correct_answer": "[5 7 9]",
    "answer_choices": [
            "[4 5 6]",
            "[1 2 3]",
            "[3 4 5]",
            "[5 7 9]"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 2 ⋅ [7 8 9]",
    "correct_answer": "[14 16 18]",
    "answer_choices": [
            "[7 8 9]",
            "[14 14 14]",
            "[16 18 20]",
            "[14 16 18]"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of P ⋅ Q, where:\nP = [[2,3],[5,6]]\nQ = [[1,4],[7,8]]",
    "correct_answer": "[[23,32],[47,68]]",
    "answer_choices": [
            "[[21,32],[42,68]]",
            "[[23,32],[46,68]]",
            "[[22,32],[47,68]]",
            "[[23,32],[47,68]]"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of M - N, where:\nM = [[9,8],[7,6]]\nN = [[5,4],[3,2]]",
    "correct_answer": "[[4,4],[4,4]]",
    "answer_choices": [
            "[[14,12],[10,8]]",
            "[[4,4],[4,5]]",
            "[[5,5],[5,5]]",
            "[[4,4],[4,4]]"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "The nodes [E F G H], are connected by edges to form the following matrix:\n\n[[0,3,2,0],[1,0,0,4],[1,1,0,1],[0,0,0,2]]\n\nFind the shortest path from E to H",
    "correct_answer": "5",
    "answer_choices": [
            "4",
            "6",
            "7",
            "5"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of R ⋅ S, where:\nR = [[2,1,3],[4,5,6]]\nS = [[1,4],[7,8],[9,2]]",
    "correct_answer": "[[36,22],[93,68]]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[[30,26],[83,56]]",
        "[[33,24],[88,59]]",
        "[[34,24],[89,57]]",
        "[[36,22],[93,68]]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Represent the following as an edge-list:\n\n[[0,1,1],[1,0,1],[1,1,0]]",
    "correct_answer": "[A1B,A1C,B1A,B1C,C1A,C1B]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[A1B,A1C,B1C,C1A,C1B]",
        "[A1B,A1C,B1A,B1C,C1A,C1B]",
        "[A1B,A1C,B1A,C1A,C1B]",
        "[A1B,A1C,B1A,B1B,C1A,C1B]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of M ⋅ N, where:\n\nM = [[3,4],[5,6]]\n\nN = [[7,8,9],[11,12,13]]",
    "correct_answer": "[[65,72,66],[101,112,123]]",
    "answer_choices": [
            "[[68,74,80],[112,124,140]]",
            "[[65,74,84],[107,124,142]]",
            "Error",
            "[[65,72,66],[101,112,123]]"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Represent the following as an edge-list:\n\n[[0,1],[1,0]]",
    "correct_answer": "[A1B,B1A]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[A1A,B1B]",
        "[A1B,B1B]",
        "[A1B,B1A]",
        "[A1A,B1A]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of T ⋅ U, where:\nT = [[7,2,1],[5,3,6]]\nU = [[1,2,3],[4,5,6]]. U needs to be transposed first.",
    "correct_answer": "[[14,44],[29,71]]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[[21,35,50],[28,52,77]]",
        "[[20,33,47],[27,50,74]]",
        "Error",
        "[[14,44],[29,71]]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of M ⋅ N, where:\nM = [[5,2],[1,3]]\nN = [[2,4],[5,6]]. M needs to be transposed first.",
    "correct_answer": "[[18,37],[13,23]]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[[9,20],[15,26]]",
        "[[10,21],[16,27]]",
        "[[13,23],[18,37]]",
        "[[18,37],[13,23]]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is 1111000 + 1010101",
    "correct_answer": "11001101",
    "answer_choices": [
            "10101010",
            "10101101",
            "10001110",
            "11001101"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of X ⋅ Y, where:\nX = [[1,3,5],[2,4,6]]\nY = [[1,2],[3,4],[5,6]]. Y needs to be transposed first.",
    "correct_answer": "[[35,44],[44,56]]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[[35,43],[45,56]]",
        "[[34,44],[44,57]]",
        "[[35,45],[44,56]]",
        "[[35,44],[44,56]]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Represent the following as an edge-list:\n\n[[0,0,1],[0,0,1],[1,1,0]]",
    "correct_answer": "[A1C,B1C,C1A,C1B]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[A1B,A1C,B1A,B1C,C1A,C1B]",
        "[A1C,B1C,C1A,C1B]",
        "[A1B,A1C,B1C,C1A]",
        "[A1C,B1C,C1B]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of A ⋅ B, where:\nA = [[7,3],[5,1]]\nB = [[1,9],[2,6]]",
    "correct_answer": "[[11,75],[7,51]]",
    "answer_choices": [
        "[[10,75],[7,50]]",
        "[[11,76],[7,51]]",
        "[[11,74],[8,51]]",
        "[[11,75],[7,51]]"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Symmetry in relation is...",
    "correct_answer": "xRy ⇒ yRx",
    "answer_choices": [
            "xRx for all x",
            "xRy, yRz ⇒ xRz",
            "x ⇒ y, y ⇒ z",
            "xRy ⇒ yRx"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of {p,q,r}∪{r,s}",
    "correct_answer": "{p,q,r,s}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{p,q,r}",
            "{p,q,r,r,s}",
            "{r,s}",
            "{p,q,r,s}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Reflexivity in relation is...",
    "correct_answer": "xRx for all x",
    "answer_choices": [
        "xRy, yRz ⇒ xRz",
        "xRy ⇒ yRx",
        "x ⇒ y, y ⇒ z",
        "xRx for all x"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "If relation S is defined by xSy where 3x = x + y then S is...",
    "correct_answer": "Reflexive,Symmetric,Transitive",
    "answer_choices": [
            "Symmetric,Transitive",
            "Reflexive,Symmetric",
            "Reflexive",
            "Reflexive,Symmetric,Transitive"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "Transitivity in relation is...",
    "correct_answer": "xRy, yRz ⇒ xRz",
    "answer_choices": [
        "xRy ⇒ yRx",
        "xRx for all x",
        "x ⇒ y, y ⇒ z",
        "xRy, yRz ⇒ xRz"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "A relation is antisymmetric if...",
    "correct_answer": "(xRy ∧ yRx) ⇒ x=y",
    "answer_choices": [
        "xRx for all x",
        "xRy, yRz ⇒ xRz",
        "(xRy ∧ yRx) ⇒ x=y",
        "xRy ⇒ yRx"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is an example of a relation that is reflexive, symmetric, and transitive?",
    "correct_answer": "Equality (=)",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Less than (<)",
        "Greater than (>)",
        "Not equal to (≠)",
        "Equality (=)"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "If we have a case where aSb AND aSc, can relation S be a function?",
    "correct_answer": "This relation is not a function",
    "answer_choices": [
            "Relations can always be functions",
            "Relations can never be functions",
            "This relation is a function",
            "This relation is not a function"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the result of 123 ⊕ 234",
    "correct_answer": "153",
    "answer_choices": [
            "167",
            "157",
            "83",
            "153"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What do you call reducing a List/Array/Set to a single value?",
    "correct_answer": "Reducing",
    "answer_choices": [
            "Folding",
            "Scaling",
            "Sweeping",
            "Reducing"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If function g(x) = x+2, then for g([2,3])=[4,5]...",
    "correct_answer": "[2,3] is domain, [4,5] is range",
    "answer_choices": [
            "[2,3] is domain, [4,5] is result",
            "[2,3] is related to result [4,5]",
            "[4,3] is domain, [5,4] is range",
            "[2,3] is domain, [4,5] is range"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "A relation is said to be reflexive, symmetric, antisymmetric and transitive. This is a...",
    "correct_answer": "Contradiction",
    "answer_choices": [
        "Possible",
        "Contradiction",
        "Always correct",
        "Case-specific"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by {t ∈ ℤ | t >= 0; t <= 6; t mod 2 = 0}",
    "correct_answer": "{0,2,4,6}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{0,2,4}",
            "{0,1,2,3,4,5,6}",
            "{0,2,4,6,8}",
            "{0,2,4,6}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the set created by:\n\n {t ∈ ℤ | t >= 1; t <= 8; t mod 2 = 0}",
    "correct_answer": "{2,4,6,8}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{1,3,5,7}",
            "{2,4,6}",
            "{2,4,6,8,10}",
            "{2,4,6,8}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If A = {1,2,3} and B = {3,4,5}, what is A ∪ B?",
    "correct_answer": "{1,2,3,4,5}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{1,2,3,4}",
            "{1,2,3,4,5}",
            "{3}",
            "{4,5}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If A = {1,2,3} and B = {3,4,5}, what is A ∩ B?",
    "correct_answer": "{3}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{1,2,3}",
            "{1,2,3,4,5}",
            "{3}",
            "{1,2}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If A = {1,2,3,4,5}, what is A' in the universal set U = {1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10}?",
    "correct_answer": "{6,7,8,9,10}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{1,2,3,4,5}",
            "{6,7,8,9,10}",
            "Ø",
            "U"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If A = {1,2,3} and B = {3,4,5}, what is A - B?",
    "correct_answer": "{1,2}",
    "answer_choices": [
            "{1,2,3}",
            "{1,2}",
            "{3,4,5}",
            "{4,5}"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If x = 5, does x ∈ ℕ?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
    "answer_choices": [
            "No",
            "Yes",
            "Only if x > 5",
            "Only if x < 5"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If x = -2, does x ∈ W?",
    "correct_answer": "No",
    "answer_choices": [
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "Only if x > 0",
            "Only if x < 0"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If x = 1/2, does x ∈ ℤ?",
    "correct_answer": "No",
    "answer_choices": [
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "Only if x is an integer",
            "Only if x is a real number"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If x = √2, does x ∈ ℝ?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
    "answer_choices": [
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "Only if x is a rational number",
            "Only if x is an irrational number"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If x = 5, is it true that x ∉ {1,2,3,4}?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
    "answer_choices": [
            "No",
            "Yes",
            "Only if x > 4",
            "Only if x < 1"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If p = True and q = False, what is p ∧ q?",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Undefined",
            "True and False"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If p = True and q = False, what is p ∨ q?",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Undefined",
            "True and False"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If p = True, what is ¬p?",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Undefined",
            "True and False"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If p = True and q = False, what is p ⊕ q?",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Undefined",
            "True and False"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If p = True and q = False, what is p ⇒ q?",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Undefined",
            "True and False"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "If p = True and q = True, what is p ⇔ q?",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "answer_choices": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Undefined",
            "True and False"
        ]
},
{
    "question": "What does O(1) mean in Big O notation?",
    "correct_answer": "Constant time complexity",
    "answer_choices": ["Linear time complexity", "Constant time complexity", "Quadratic time complexity", "Logarithmic time complexity"]
},
{
    "question": "What does O(n) mean in Big O notation?",
    "correct_answer": "Linear time complexity",
    "answer_choices": ["Linear time complexity", "Constant time complexity", "Quadratic time complexity", "Logarithmic time complexity"]
},
{
    "question": "What does O(n^2) mean in Big O notation?",
    "correct_answer": "Quadratic time complexity",
    "answer_choices": ["Linear time complexity", "Constant time complexity", "Quadratic time complexity", "Logarithmic time complexity"]
},
{
    "question": "What does O(log n) mean in Big O notation?",
    "correct_answer": "Logarithmic time complexity",
    "answer_choices": ["Linear time complexity", "Constant time complexity", "Quadratic time complexity", "Logarithmic time complexity"]
},
{
    "question": "What does O(n log n) mean in Big O notation?",
    "correct_answer": "Logarithmic linear time complexity",
    "answer_choices": ["Linear time complexity", "Constant time complexity", "Quadratic time complexity", "Logarithmic linear time complexity"]
},

{
    "question": "What time complexity does binary search have?",
    "correct_answer": "O(log n)",
    "answer_choices": ["O(n)", "O(log n)", "O(1)", "O(n^2)"]
},
{
    "question": "What time complexity does bubble sort have in its worst case?",
    "correct_answer": "O(n^2)",
    "answer_choices": ["O(n)", "O(log n)", "O(1)", "O(n^2)"]
},
{
    "question": "What time complexity does a hashtable insertion and deletion have?",
    "correct_answer": "O(1)",
    "answer_choices": ["O(n)", "O(log n)", "O(1)", "O(n^2)"]
},
{
    "question": "What time complexity does a sequential search have in its worst case?",
    "correct_answer": "O(n)",
    "answer_choices": ["O(n)", "O(log n)", "O(1)", "O(n^2)"]
}
]

# print(len(questions_data))